Let's return to the equity market and what are the
brokerage houses' reports today,
which sectors, and which stocks
should you keep an eye on? That marksheet is telling us.
We are reporting on Five Star Business from Nava,
and they say that the
company has strong asset quality
despite the loan income on the group landing.
They see a very good market opportunity in this space,
but there are
operational challenges as well. They are expanding their branches in this space. The
company has strong
underwriting, and collections are an
important factor that will remain
essential for the Five Star Business. Therefore,
positive factors are being seen for Nusam,
and they have started coverage,
they have set a target of 710, and in fact, they
see an episode potential of about 35%
with the Karnal market price. Apart from this,
real estate will also remain in focus because the
Jaypee model believes that the market
dynamics are still
looking very positive for adolescents, quite attractive. In
fact, we are seeing that office gross
listing volumes are slightly  While prices are falling,
risks of a slowdown may still remain.
Developers can deliver strong pre-sales growth.
If
we focus on Bank of India, we'll now see a
report from Morgan Stanley.
In the last two months, we've seen the
stock correct 24%. Following this,
they believe the share price could rise.
Compared to the industry, Bank of India is
well-placed, according to them,
due to its strong balance sheet and attractive risk appetite.
Morgan Stanley has
maintained an overweight rating on Bank of India. The target is
125%, which means the market price is
87%. Potential upset is visible
in Bank of India. Furthermore,
we'll focus on fashion. Citi believes
that valuations of all consumer durables and
retail companies have corrected,
and as a result, they have marginally revised their earnings. The
multiple for lifestyle has been reduced from 18 times to
15 times, maintaining a
buy rating.  We have increased
our target price
from 405 to
3007%,
so there is the sector and the browser as well and
we will discuss these in detail later.